Be one.
Daniel, Simon and Millie are talking about making friends.
Listen to their conversation and tick the advice mentioned in their talk.
What do you think is the best way to make friends?
I think one of the best ways to make friends is to join a club.
Yes, I agree.
When you join a club, you'll meet people with the same interests as you.
True, that way you'll have a lot to talk about.
But you'll need to be brave to speak to other people at the club.
Yes, it's important to be friendly and to smile at people.
Another good place to make friends is the school dining hall.
You can sit next to someone and start a cheerful chat with them.
Yes, or you can ask a friend to introduce you to someone else.
That's a good idea, but it takes time to make friends, so don't give up if it doesn't happen quickly. That's true.